

# **ABOUT ME**

A diligent and enthusiastic UX-designer with experience in front-developement and has a strong passion wthin Interaction and Graphic Design.

As an individual I am friendly, honest and adventurous.

My main passion lays within curious to learn more. Other passions include art, writing and walks in nature.

# **WEBSITE & SOCIAL LINKS**

LinkedIn

<u>Portfolio</u>

# **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

Fluent

Swedish

Fluent

Thai

Proficient

# Angelic Andersson

- Junior UX-Designer

073 8 716 820

Västanvindsgatan 6A, Göteborg •

## **EDUCATION**

## IT-Högskolan

Gothenburg Aug 2021 - Present

# **EC Utbildning**

Gothenburg Sep 2019 - May 2021

# **UX- Designer**

- The program focuses on interaction design, digital design, UI designing, agile work methologies, persona & situationas work shops and advanced user centered design & prototyping products.
- The education includes 6 months of intership with a focus of gaining real work experience.

# **Frontend Developer**

- Main topics were fundamentals of web development, front end frameworks, UX/UI, Agile work and surface level backend/database courses.
- The education also includes 6 month period of internship with an aim to gain work experience upon graduation.

## Before INTERSHIP I will know:

# UX/UI + Graphic Design

Figma — — — — Adobe XD

Design Thinking

#### **Frontend**

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

React

#### **Graphic Design**

After Effects Photoshop



## **Work Methodologies**

Agile Scrum
Kanban

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Ericsson

Gotheburg Oct 2020 - May 2021



#### Frontend Developer Intern

• Creation of wireframe, mockup and implementation of frontend as well as backend with database.

#### Humblebee

Gothenburg Oct 2020 - May 2021



## **HIVE Internship**

 Usage of API from the client in order to create the final prototype called "Beem". By the end of HIVE we had a finished MVP.

#### **HOBBIES**

Cooking

Digital editing & Interaction Design

Games

Walks in nature

Book writing